

PROFILE

Innovative, optimized solution seeker. Excited to be at the deployment phase of my new career as a Full-stack web developer. I am ambitious, adventurous, assiduous, animated, and an alliteration advocate.

My work experience has given me the knowledge and skills to quickly adapt to changing circumstances and continue achieving the best performance.

PHONE:

+91 8092766575

shubham14p3@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO

HACKERRANK

GITHUB

LINKEDIN

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Critical Thinking

AWARDS

- Best employee of the year
- Techfest coder

PERSONAL INFO

Address:

H. No-21, Radha Kunj, Jyoti Nagar,Radhika Nagar, Kharangajhar, Telco,Jamshedpur, Jharkhand, India - 831004

SHUBHAM RAJ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

SKILLS

Front-End: JavaScript, React, Redux, HTML5, CSS3

Back-End: Ruby, Rails, RSpec, MySQL

Tools & Methods: Git, GitHub, Heroku, Netlify, Bitbucket, Gitlab **Professional:** Remote Pair-Programming, Teamwork, Mentoring

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Gammastack, Indore

05-2020 – continuing

- Developing a ReactJS base application.
- Working in MERN Stack development.
- Learning new Front-End Web Technologies like NextJS & Typescript

Front End Developer

Datamites Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore

08-2019 - 05-2020

- Engaged in client communication for all-important.
- Performed Data cleansing/transformation, feature engineering.
- Developed and implemented advanced analytics approaches.

Software Engineer

Nagravision India Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore

07-2018 - 07-2019

- System Acceptance Testing and Program delivery.
- Reporting Tests and Technical documentation.
- Implemented STB automated test lab environments.

PROJECTS

- <u>Inncodesolutions</u> Hosting Website Solution created on React.
- Fillurbasket E-commerce Website created on React.
- <u>DBZ</u> Shooting Game made with Phaser, JS and testing with JEST.
- <u>TicTacToe</u> Tic-Tac Toe with Vanilla Js & testing with JEST.
- <u>Techno-Article</u> Article website created with Ruby on Rails.

EDUCATION

Microverse

Remote Full Stack Web Development Program

Feb 2020 – Continuing

- Spent 1300+ hours mastering algorithms, data structures, and full-stack development while simultaneously developing projects with Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, React, and Redux.
- Developed skills in remote pair-programming using GitHub, industrystandard gitflow, and daily standups to communicate and collaborate with international remote developers

Bhilai Institute of Technology

Bachelor in Engineering with Computer Science Engineering

2014-2018

- Followed my passion in Software Development and completed Bachelor Engineering in Computer Science & Engineering.
- Represented my College in many national and domestic events.

Vidya Bharati Chinmaya Vidyalaya

10 + 2 with Science

2001 - 2014

 President of the school, facilitated monthly meetings to enhance a diverse community. Managed activities like monthly talks, workshops, and student panels.